In this Developer Basics video, we
この開発者向け 基本ビデオでは
are going to take a close look at all
高度なプレーヤーおよび インページ・プレーヤーの
the attributes of the advanced or in-page player
実装コードの全ての 属性を
implementation code.
詳しく見ていきます。
This code is commonly used, but there
ほとんどのコードは一般的に 使用されていますが
are a few attributes that almost no one thoroughly understands.
いくつかの属性を 完全に理解している人はほとんどいません。
Let's take a look at the player code copied from Studio
では、動画を公開するために スタジオからコピーした
that publishes the video.
プレーヤーのコードを見てみましょう。
The code has been formatted a bit using best practice
このコードは、インデント規則の ベストプラクティスに従って、
indentation convention.
少し体裁を整えてあります。
First, let's go quickly through the attributes
まず、一般的に 知られている属性について
that are commonly understood--
簡単に見ていきましょう。
data-account for the account number,
data-accountは、 アカウント番号を指定します。
data-player for the player ID, data-video--id for the video ID
data-playerは、プレーヤーIDを指定します。 data-video--idは、プレーヤーに読み込む
of the video to load in the player, width and height,
ビデオIDを指定します。 widthとheightはプレーヤの幅と高さです。
data-playlist-id for the playlist
data-playlist-idは、プレイリストIDを指定します。
ID that will work if the player is configured to play playlist.
これはプレイリストを再生するように 設定されている場合に動作します。
By the way, if you have a playlist ID,
ちなみに プレイリストIDが指定されている場合、
you cannot also supply a video ID.
ビデオIDを指定することはできません。
An error will result. You can use the data-playlist-video-id
指定した場合、エラーになります。 この場合、data-playlist-video-idを使用すると
with the playlist.
プレイリストと一緒に指定することができます。
That attribute lets you set the initial video
この属性で プレイリスト内で再生する
to play in the playlist.
最初の動画を設定します。
It lets you pick any video in the playlist
プレイリスト中から任意の ビデオを選んで、
to be the initial video that is played.
最初に再生される の動画を指定することができます。
Now we get to look at some attributes that
では、もう少し面白い属性と、
are a little more interesting, and one
ほとんど使用されない
that is very rarely used.
属性を見てみましょう。
The controls= the empty string attribute is a Boolean
controls= 空文字列 は真偽値属性で、
attribute which defines if the controls should
プレーヤーに コントロールを
be shown in the player or not.
表示するかどうかを定義します。
In earlier versions of the generated code,
以前のバージョンで 生成されたコードでは、
simply the word "controls" would appear with no equal sign
単に "controls "という単語が 等号と引用符なしで
and quote quote.
表示されていました。
That still works, by the way.
ちなみにこれでも動きます。
You can also have controls="fish,"
また controls="fish," としても
and that works.
動作します。
You can even say controls="false,"
さらに controls="false, " としても
and the controls will show up.
コントロールは表示されます。
If you don't want the controls to appear,
コントロールを表示させたくない場合は、
simply remove any variation of that attribute.
その属性のバリエーションを削除してください。
Next on the list of sometimes misunderstood attributes
次に、 誤解されやすい属性として
is data-application-id.
data-application-id があります。
This is for use with analytics.
これはアナリティクスで使用するためのものです。
This attribute lets you use the same player on multiple web
この属性を使用すると 複数のWebページで
pages but get different player analytics
同じプレーヤーを使用しても 各ページでの使用に対して
data for its use on each page.
異なるプレーヤー解析データを 取得することができます。
For instance, you could have, on three different pages,
例えば、以下のように 3つの異なるページに
data-application-id="home," data application id="contact us,"
data-application-id="home," data-application-id="contact us,"
and data-application-id="faqs."
data-application-id="faqs."を配置することが可能です。
The analytics would be reported separately for each HTML page,
3つのページで同じプレーヤーが使われていても 分析結果は、HTMLページごとに
even though the same player is used on all three pages.
個別に報告されることになります。
This is very useful and regularly used
これは非常に便利な機能で
for accurate player analytics.
正確なプレイヤー分析としてよく使用されています。
The data-embed-attribute is very seldom used and therefore
data-embed属性は、あまり使用されていないので
not well understood.
よく理解されていない属性の１つです。
The attribute reflects parent-child relationships
この属性はプレーヤーとの 親子関係が
with players.
反映される属性です。
That's it, and even probably more detail than you
以上が、高度なプレーヤーの
wanted to know about the advanced player implementation
実装コードについての
code.
説明になります。